Jenna S. Rotolo

jrotolo811@gmail.com | (631) 786-4363

Dear hiring manager,

I am a recent graduate from SUNY Oswego, with a Bachelor of Science in Business Administration. During my last semester of my undergraduate studies, I had the opportunity to be a Marketing/Communications Intern for Citnalta Construction Corp., a general contracting firm based in Bohemia, NY. This experience opened doors and sparked high interest for me in construction, specifically public sector work.

During my time at Citnalta, I was guided closely by the Marketing and Proposal Manager and taught everything about the construction industry. Not only did this give me valuable experience handling marketing tasks, including the maintenance of social media platforms and graphic design, but proposal tasks as well. My internship project, that continued throughout the duration of my time there, was to create a mock version of a previously submitted Statement of Qualifications (SOQ). I utilized Adobe InDesign to design graphic components for this mock proposal, and wrote my own narrative sections as well. Additionally, I utilized Adobe Acrobat for the organization and development of this 200+ page document. This process allowed me to become deeply familiar with public New York agencies such as Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA), New York School Construction Authority (NYSCA), and New York City Transit (NYCT), through the process of deeply analyzing documents such as Request For Proposals (RFP).

My time as an intern also included frequent site visits to multiple MTA and NYCSCA projects in the New York City and Long Island Area. Being able to experience this type of exposure to construction has only strengthened my interest in the industry and proposal work as a whole. Because of my experience in public sector construction, I believe I would be a great fit for the role of Marketing Coordinator at MP Engineers & Architects, and I would be thrilled to be selected for an interview.

Thank you for taking the time to review my application.

Sincerely, Jenna Rotolo



Contact

Phone: 631-786-4363

Email: jrotolo811@gmail.com

Technical Skills

- Adobe Creative Suite
 - InDesign
 - Acrobat
- HootSuite
- Meta Business Suite
- MailChimp
- Canva
- Microsoft Office
 - PowerPoint
 - Excel
 - Word
 - Teams
 - Outlook
- · Google Ads Dashboard

Involvement

Figure Skating Club of New York (SCNY)

Jenna S. Rotolo

Hardworking go-getter with a range of professional capabilities. Strong creative eye with a passion for marketing and media.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

PS Digital, Hauppauge, NY Marketing Associate May 2023 - Present

- Create Google Ad campaigns for clients in a wide range of industries
- Formulate and develop marketing strategies based on data analytics
- · Monitor and maintain full client database
- Evaluate financial aspects of client profiles such as budget, bidding strategies, conversions, and ROI

Citnalta Construction Corp., Bohemia, NY Marketing/Communications Intern January 2023 - May 2023

- · Published written and graphic design content
- Managed social media platforms (LinkedIn, Instagram, Facebook)
- · Developed and maintain detailed social media calendar
- Contributed pieces for company newsletter and website
- · Acquired and organize photo and video content for company database
- Created and distribute promotional content for marketing campaigns
- Designed advertisements for company sponsorships
- · Worked closely with executives and upper-level management
- Independently developed project proposal

SUNY Oswego School Of Business, Oswego, NY Teaching Assistant

August 2022 - December 2022

- Coordinated grading, management, and development of assignments
- Managed and conducted daily class attendance and announcements
- Responsible for creating lesson plans and teaching select classes
- Developed and facilitated in-class educational activities
- Developed knowledge in organizational behavior, presentation skills, and ability to effectively communicate and lead others

NOTABLE CONTRIBUTONS

Women's Builders Council (WBC)

Opening Doors Wider 2023 - Top legislative Issues: MWBE Certification in NYS Recomended Solutions for Change

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration

State University of New York at Oswego, Oswego, NY